

"Hello Steem World," 

"I am thankful to the code creators and my son for getting me this far. In general I appreciate the world wide web for what I continue to learn from numerous indy blog, vlog and pod producers. I have made a few videos myself but primarily I consume rather than create media these days. Indeed, pulling together this introduction has challenged me a tad."

"I don't usually look so fancy, I am playing dress-up with my daughter."

"I intend to share and grow my knowledge of gardening, healthy eating and home schooling. I cherish time outside in the garden. I let myself be instructed by the elements: smelling the dirt as it soaks in the rain. I love seeds, baby plants, compost and even weeds. I am a feet in the dirt funky kinda woman."

"Right now the counter and fridge are full and overflowing with pickles and dilly beans" 

"Half sour pickles are unbelievably easy to make. They require cucumbers, salt, water, garlic and dill. The only processing required is to taste them once in a while. After four weeks they will need to be moved into the fridge. It is an amazing culture creation: and perhaps not unlike Steemit will be."

"I cherish my two children and loving husband. When I am not serving them pickles or lemon apple juice pops, I can be found in the garden, the kitchen or the dance studio. My husband creates funky music & functional art from clay and wood. Eventually we want to create a family business of functional art productions." 

"I anticipate a bright future for a Steem Scene that allows proper flow and connections between the providers and their content. If the platform remains uncensored and uncontrolled, I think SteemIt has the potential of bringing social media to a new level. I want to be t(here)."

"8.15.16"

"Thanks for developing such a cool tool steem team!" 
  
 